Achieve all your retirement dreams and aspirations with our new plan
that will let you restart your life
and
live on your own terms without worrying about retirement. Introducing
ICICI Prudential Guaranteed Pension Plan
Flexi, a regular payout flexible
annuity plan designed to help you gradually
build retirement savings and receive
a guaranteed regular income for your post-retirement life.
Let's understand
how the plan works.
You will start receiving a guaranteed lifelong income after completion of the Single Life Deferment Term with return of premium.
In case of your unfortunate demise, the
death benefit will be paid to the nominees and the
policy will terminate.
You will start receiving a guaranteed lifelong income after completion of the Joint Life Deferment Term with return of premium.
In case of your unfortunate demise, your family member will continue to receive the
same income for life. In case of
unfortunate demise of both you and the family member, the
death benefit will be paid to the nominees
and the policy will terminate. You will start receiving a guaranteed lifelong income after completion of the
Single Life Deferment Term with booster payouts.  In
addition to the guaranteed income, you will also get back
50% of your total premiums paid as booster payouts.
Please note: The first
booster payout will be made on the fifth policy anniversary after the term.
Thereafter, booster payouts will be made every 5 years on the policy anniversary.
You will be paid a maximum of
five such payouts. The amount of each booster
payout will
be equal to 10% of the total premiums paid.
In case of your unfortunate demise, the
nominee will be given a death benefit.
With the Accelerated Health Booster,
you will start
receiving a guaranteed lifetime income after the completion of the Single Life Deferment Period. In
addition to the guaranteed income, the
total premiums paid will be returned to
you in 10 instalments as Accelerated Health Boosters on diagnosis of inability to perform at least three out of six activities of daily living.
Please note: Each Accelerated
Health Booster will be
equal to 10% of the total premiums paid
and will be paid for a period of 10 years or
till the date of death, whichever is earlier.
You will continue to receive the base annuity even after the expiry of the Accelerated Health Booster.
Premium on Critical Illness or Permanent Disability due to accident or death  You will start receiving a guaranteed lifetime income after completion of
Single Life deferment period with return of premium In
addition to the guaranteed income, on diagnosis of a specified critical
illness, permanent disability or death, the
total premiums paid will be
returned to you or the nominee After completion of
Single Life deferment period without return of premium,
you will start receiving a guaranteed lifetime income
In case of your unfortunate demise during the deferment period, a benefit
amount known as death benefit will be
payable to the nominee
In case of death after the deferment period, no death benefit will be payable and the policy will
terminate After
completion of Joint Life deferment period without return of premium,
you will start receiving a guaranteed lifetime income
In case of your unfortunate demise, your family member will continue to
receive the same income throughout his/her life
In the absence of both you and the family member,
a benefit amount known as death benefit will be
payable to the nominee during the deferment period Thereafter, no
further benefits will be payable and the policy will terminate In case of
your or
any family member's death after the deferment period,
no death benefit will be payable
After completion of the Joint Life Deferment Period,
you will start receiving a guaranteed lifelong income with return of premium and waiver of premium.
In case of your unfortunate demise,
your family member will continue to receive the same income throughout his/her life.
In case of your unfortunate demise, the
death benefit will be payable to the nominee and the
policy will terminate. In case of
your unfortunate demise during the premium paying term,
future premiums will be waived
and your family member will continue to receive the
same income throughout his/her life.
After completion of the Joint Life Deferment Period, you will start
receiving a guaranteed lifelong income with return of premium and waiver of premium.
In case of your unfortunate demise, your family member will continue to receive the same income throughout his/her life.
During the deferment period,
in the absence of both you and the family member, a benefit amount
known as death benefit will be
payable to the nominee. Thereafter,
no further benefits will be payable and the policy will terminate.
After the deferment period, no death benefit will be payable in case of your or
any family member's death
during the premium paying term.
In the event of your unfortunate demise,
future premiums will be waived off with the waiver of premium benefit
and your family member will continue to receive the
same guaranteed income throughout their life
and you have your
retirement planning sorted
[Music]